Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- John DiBiaggio, administrative records and related papers, 1976 -- 2005; 1990 -- 2001; UA001.014; 49.2 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Subject files, 1976 -- 2005; 1990 -- 1996; UA001.014.001; 42.0 Linear Feet
    - Provost, 2000; UA001.014.001.027.00042 (Box 27)
    - Public safety, 1985 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.027.00043 (Box 27)
    - Public safety, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.027.00044 (Box 27)
    - Public safety, 1993 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.027.00045 (Box 27)
    - Public safety, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.027.00046 (Box 27)
    - "Q" general, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - "R" general, 1982 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - "R" general, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - "R" general, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00004 (Box 28)
    - Racism, 1985 -- 1988; UA001.014.001.028.00005 (Box 28)
    - Recommendations, 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00006 (Box 28)
    - Research, 1986 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.028.00007 (Box 28)
    - Reserve Officer's Training Corps, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00008 (Box 28)
    - Reserve Officer's Training Corps, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00009 (Box 28)
    - Reserve Officer's Training Corps, 1995 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00010 (Box 28)
    - Reserve Officer's Training Corps, 1996 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.028.00011 (Box 28)
    - Residential life, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00012 (Box 28)
    - Residential life, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.028.00013 (Box 28)
    - Resumes, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00014 (Box 28)
    - Resumes, 1993 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.028.00015 (Box 28)
    - Resumes, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00016 (Box 28)
    - Rhode Island Children's Crusade for Higher Education, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.028.00017 (Box 28)
    - "S" general, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00018 (Box 28)
    - "S" general, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00019 (Box 28)
    - "S" general, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00020 (Box 28)
    - "S" general, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00021 (Box 28)
    - Sabbaticals, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00022 (Box 28)
    - Sackler, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
    - Sackler, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00024 (Box 28)
    - Sackler: admissions, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00025 (Box 28)
    - Sackler: alumni relations, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00026 (Box 28)
    - Sackler Center for Health Communications, 1986; UA001.014.001.028.00027 (Box 28)
    - Sackler Center for Health Communications, 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00028 (Box 28)
    - Saint Elizabeth's Medical Center, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.028.00029 (Box 28)
    - Salaries, 1983 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.028.00030 (Box 28)
    - Salzburg Seminar, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00031 (Box 28)
    - Schmidheiny, 1999; UA001.014.001.028.00032 (Box 28)
    - Scholarships, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.028.00033 (Box 28)
    - Scholarships, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.028.00034 (Box 28)
    - School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1993; UA001.014.001.029.00001 (Box 29)
    - School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.029.00002 (Box 29)
    - Schience Coalition, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.029.00003 (Box 29)
    - Science and technology center, 1985 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.029.00004 (Box 29)
    - Scrolls, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.029.00005 (Box 29)
    - Second Nature, 2000; UA001.014.001.029.00006 (Box 29)
    - Senior class gift, 1992 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.029.00007 (Box 29)
    - Senior survey, 1994; UA001.014.001.029.00008 (Box 29)
    - Senior survey, 1998; UA001.014.001.029.00009 (Box 29)
    - Senior survey, 1999; UA001.014.001.029.00010 (Box 29)
    - Sexual harassment, 1984 -- 1989; UA001.014.001.029.00011 (Box 29)
    - Shevardnadze, 1999; UA001.014.001.029.00012 (Box 29)
    - South Africa, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.029.00013 (Box 29)
    - South Africa: divestment, 1985 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.029.00014 (Box 29)
    - South Africa: scholarships, 1985 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.029.00015 (Box 29)
    - South Africa: scholarships, 1992; UA001.014.001.029.00016 (Box 29)
    - Southern New England Consortium on Race and Ethnicity, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.029.00017 (Box 29)
    - Strategic review, 1991; UA001.014.001.029.00018 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.029.00019 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.029.00020 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.029.00021 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.029.00022 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.029.00023 (Box 29)
    - Student activities, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.029.00024 (Box 29)
    - Students, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.029.00025 (Box 29)
    - Students, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.029.00026 (Box 29)
    - Student activities: yearbook, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.029.00027 (Box 29)
    - Student Coalition for Investment Responsibility at Tufts, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.030.00001 (Box 30)
    - Student leaders reception, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.030.00002 (Box 30)
    - Student news conference, 1997; UA001.014.001.030.00003 (Box 30)
    - Student newspapers, 1988 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.030.00004 (Box 30)
    - Student newspapers, 1992 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00005 (Box 30)
    - Student newspapers: clippings, 1995 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Student policies, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00007 (Box 30)
    - Student senate, 1985 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - Student senate, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.030.00009 (Box 30)
    - Student services initiative, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.030.00010 (Box 30)
    - Students, 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - Students, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.030.00012 (Box 30)
    - Students: alcohol, drugs, etc., 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00013 (Box 30)
    - Study 24/7, 2000; UA001.014.001.030.00014 (Box 30)
    - Study of Sports in Society, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.030.00015 (Box 30)
    - Sullivan Principles, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00016 (Box 30)
    - Summer jobs, 1984 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00017 (Box 30)
    - Summer school, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.030.00018 (Box 30)
    - Surveys, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.030.00019 (Box 30)
    - Surveys, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00020 (Box 30)
    - Sylvanus Packard Society, 1993; UA001.014.001.030.00021 (Box 30)
    - "T" general, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00022 (Box 30)
    - Talloires, 1988 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.030.00023 (Box 30)
    - Talloires, 1995; UA001.014.001.030.00024 (Box 30)
    - Talloires, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00025 (Box 30)
    - Task force on race, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.030.00026 (Box 30)
    - Task force on race, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.030.00027 (Box 30)
    - Task force on race: arts and sciences oversight panel, 1998; UA001.014.001.030.00028 (Box 30)
    - Teacher of the year, 1985 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.030.00029 (Box 30)
    - Teacher of the year, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.030.00030 (Box 30)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1996; UA001.014.001.030.00031 (Box 30)
    - Telecommunications, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Telecom City, 1997; UA001.014.001.031.00002 (Box 31)
    - Tenure and promotion, 1989 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Text wizards, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.031.00004 (Box 31)
    - TIAA-CREF, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00005 (Box 31)
    - Tiger's Tale, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.031.00006 (Box 31)
    - Tokai University, 1991; UA001.014.001.031.00007 (Box 31)
    - Troika, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.031.00008 (Box 31)
    - Troika, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.031.00009 (Box 31)
    - Troika, 1996 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.031.00010 (Box 31)
    - Troika, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00011 (Box 31)
    - Tufts: general, 1984 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.031.00012 (Box 31)
    - Tufts art collections, 1991 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.031.00013 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Associated Health Plan, 1985 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.031.00014 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Associated Health Plan, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.031.00015 (Box 31)
    - Tufts biotechnology park, 1985 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.031.00016 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Black Alumni Association, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.031.00017 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Christian Fellowship, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00018 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Christian Fellowship, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00019 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Christian Fellowship, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00020 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Club, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.031.00021 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Club, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00022 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Appeal, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00023 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Appeal, 1998; UA001.014.001.031.00024 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Appeal, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00025 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Union Judiciary: Senate issues/resolutions, 1999; UA001.014.001.031.00026 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Union Judiciary: Senate reference, 1999; UA001.014.001.031.00027 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Community Union Judiciary: Larry Harris, president, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00028 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Criterion, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.031.00029 (Box 31)
    - Tufts descendants, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.031.00030 (Box 31)
    - Tufts employees, 1984 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.031.00031 (Box 31)
    - Tufts fellows, 2000; UA001.014.001.031.00032 (Box 31)
    - Tufts history, 1976 -- 1985; UA001.014.001.031.00033 (Box 31)
    - Tufts history, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.031.00034 (Box 31)
    - Tufts history, 1985 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.031.00035 (Box 31)
    - Tufts Jumbo Club, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - Tufts Jumbo Club, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.032.00002 (Box 32)
    - Tufts Kinsmen, 1985 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.032.00003 (Box 32)
    - Tufts Neighborhood Fund, 1995; UA001.014.001.032.00004 (Box 32)
    - Tufts programs abroad, 1985 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - Tufts programs abroad: London, 1983 -- 1988; UA001.014.001.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - Tufts programs abroad: Paris, 1986 -- 1989; UA001.014.001.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - Tufts programs abroad: Talloires, 1986 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - Tufts programs abroad: Tubingen, 1984 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00009 (Box 32)
    - Tufts review, 1997; UA001.014.001.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - Tufts review, 1997; UA001.014.001.032.00011 (Box 32)
    - Tufts review, 1996 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.032.00012 (Box 32)
    - Tufts television, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.032.00013 (Box 32)
    - Tufts University Development Committee, 1989 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.032.00014 (Box 32)
    - Tufts University Development Committee, 1990 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00015 (Box 32)
    - Tufts University Development Committee, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.032.00016 (Box 32)
    - Tuition, 1976 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00017 (Box 32)
    - "U" general, 1983 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.032.00018 (Box 32)
    - "U" general, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.032.00019 (Box 32)
    - Undergraduate education, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.032.00020 (Box 32)
    - Union matters, 1988 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.032.00021 (Box 32)
    - Unicco, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.032.00022 (Box 32)
    - Unicco, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.032.00023 (Box 32)
    - United Nations, 2000; UA001.014.001.032.00024 (Box 32)
    - United Nations Development Programme, 1994; UA001.014.001.032.00025 (Box 32)
    - United Nations Environmental Programme, 1993 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.032.00026 (Box 32)
    - United Nations Environmental Programme, 1999; UA001.014.001.032.00027 (Box 32)
    - United States Congress, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.032.00028 (Box 32)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00029 (Box 32)
    - United States Department of Education, 1987 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00030 (Box 32)
    - United States Department of Education, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.032.00031 (Box 32)
    - United States Department of Education, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.032.00032 (Box 32)
    - United States Department of State, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00033 (Box 32)
    - United States government: general, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00034 (Box 32)
    - United States House of Representatives, 1984 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.032.00035 (Box 32)
    - United States House of Representatives, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.032.00036 (Box 32)
    - Tufts Report on Annual Giving, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.032.00037 (Box Shared 35)
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.033.00001 (Box 33)
    - U.S. 500th anniversary celebration, 1988 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.033.00002 (Box 33)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1988 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.033.00003 (Box 33)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.033.00004 (Box 33)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1991 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.033.00005 (Box 33)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1996 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00006 (Box 33)
    - U.S. News and World Report, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00007 (Box 33)
    - U.S. Senate, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.033.00008 (Box 33)
    - U.S. Senate, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00009 (Box 33)
    - United Way, 1988 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.033.00010 (Box 33)
    - United Way, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00011 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service, 1997; UA001.014.001.033.00012 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service, 1998; UA001.014.001.033.00013 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service, 1999; UA001.014.001.033.00014 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service, 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00015 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: advisory board, 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00016 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: advisory committee meeting, 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00017 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: class assignments, 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00018 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: leadership class, 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00019 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: leadership seminar, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00020 (Box 33)
    - University College of Citizenship and Public Service: public relations media, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00021 (Box 33)
    - University of Cape Town Fund/Open Society Scholars Fund, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00022 (Box 33)
    - University College, Cork: conference on famine, 1995; UA001.014.001.033.00023 (Box 33)
    - University College, Cork: conference on famine, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.033.00024 (Box 33)
    - University council, 1999; UA001.014.001.033.00025 (Box 33)
    - University council, 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00026 (Box 33)
    - University council, 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00027 (Box 33)
    - University Leaders for a Sustainable Future, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.033.00028 (Box 33)
    - University organization, 1983 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.033.00029 (Box 33)
    - University Partnership for Infant and Toddler Professionals, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.033.00030 (Box 33)
    - University policies, 1985 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.033.00031 (Box 33)
    - University policies, 1992 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00001 (Box 34)
    - University Press of New England, 1993 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.034.00002 (Box 34)
    - Universities Research Association, 1982 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.034.00003 (Box 34)
    - Universities Research Association, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.034.00004 (Box 34)
    - Universities Research Association, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00005 (Box 34)
    - University Year 2000 compliance task force, 1998; UA001.014.001.034.00006 (Box 34)
    - Urban and environmental policy, 1995; UA001.014.001.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - "V" general, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.034.00008 (Box 34)
    - "V" general, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1993; UA001.014.001.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1990 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1995; UA001.014.001.034.00013 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1995; UA001.014.001.034.00014 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.034.00015 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.034.00016 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00017 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00018 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school: admissions, 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00019 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school: alumni relations, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.034.00020 (Box 34)
    - Veterinary school: appropriations, 1993 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.034.00021 (Box 34)
    - Vision, 1994; UA001.014.001.034.00022 (Box 34)
    - Vision, 1994; UA001.014.001.034.00023 (Box 34)
    - Vision: medical, 1994; UA001.014.001.034.00024 (Box 34)
    - Vision: monthly reports, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00025 (Box 34)
    - "W" general, 1992; UA001.014.001.034.00026 (Box 34)
    - "W" general, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.034.00027 (Box 34)
    - "W" general, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.034.00028 (Box 34)
    - "W" general, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.034.00029 (Box 34)
    - Walnut Hill-6, 1984 -- 1986; UA001.014.001.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - Washington Advisory Group, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.035.00002 (Box 35)
    - Weber Group, 1997; UA001.014.001.035.00003 (Box 35)
    - Wessell letters, 1996; UA001.014.001.035.00004 (Box 35)
    - Wessell letters-7, 1996 -- 1997; UA001.014.001.035.00005 (Box 35)
    - White paper, 1994; UA001.014.001.035.00006 (Box 35)
    - Who's Who in America, 2000; UA001.014.001.035.00007 (Box 35)
    - Who's Who in the World, 2000; UA001.014.001.035.00008 (Box 35)
    - Wingspread-9, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.035.00009 (Box 35)
    - Women's studies, 1987 -- 1989; UA001.014.001.035.00010 (Box 35)
    - Women's studies-6, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.035.00011 (Box 35)
    - Wright Center-5, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.036.00001 (Box 36)
    - Writing across the curriculum program, 1992; UA001.014.001.036.00002 (Box 36)
    - "X, Y, Z" general-8, 1983 -- 1988; UA001.014.001.036.00003 (Box 36)
    - "Y" general-5, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.036.00004 (Box 36)
    - "Y" general, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.036.00005 (Box 36)
    - "Z" general-6, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.036.00006 (Box 36)
    - Zoos, 1986; UA001.014.001.036.00007 (Box 36)
    - NESCAC [1of2], 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00001 (Box 46)
    - NESCAC [2of2], 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00002 (Box 46)
    - African American Center, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00003 (Box 46)
    - Art Gallery, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00004 (Box 46)
    - Asian American Center, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00005 (Box 46)
    - CSDD- Center for the Study od Drug Development, 1985 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00008 (Box 46)
    - Center on Hunger, Poverty, and Nutrition Policy, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00009 (Box 46)
    - Global Development and Environment Institute, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00010 (Box 46)
    - Hispanic American Center, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00011 (Box 46)
    - Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Resource Center, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00012 (Box 46)
    - Lincoln-Filene Center, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00013 (Box 46)
    - Wright Center for Science Education, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00014 (Box 46)
    - Boston Campus Rooms, 1998; UA001.014.001.046.00015 (Box 46)
    - [Athletics], 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00016 (Box 46)
    - Physical Education Athletics [1of2], 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00017 (Box 46)
    - Physical Education Athletics [2of2], 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00018 (Box 46)
    - American Studies, 1982 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00019 (Box 46)
    - Biology, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.046.00020 (Box 46)
    - Chemistry, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00021 (Box 46)
    - Child Study, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00022 (Box 46)
    - Classics, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00023 (Box 46)
    - Communications Department, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.046.00024 (Box 46)
    - Drama and Dance, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00025 (Box 46)
    - Economics, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00026 (Box 46)
    - Education, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00027 (Box 46)
    - Engineering, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00028 (Box 46)
    - English (Departmental), 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00029 (Box 46)
    - History, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00030 (Box 46)
    - International Relations, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00031 (Box 46)
    - Music, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00032 (Box 46)
    - Peace and Justice Studies, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00033 (Box 46)
    - Philosophy, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00034 (Box 46)
    - Physics/Astronomy, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00035 (Box 46)
    - Political Science, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.046.00036 (Box 46)
    - Religion, 1999; UA001.014.001.046.00037 (Box 46)
    - Romance Languages, 1997; UA001.014.001.046.00038 (Box 46)
    - Urban and Environmental Policy, 2000; UA001.014.001.046.00039 (Box 46)
    - Akbarian, Mohammed, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00001 (Box 47)
    - Ames, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00002 (Box 47)
    - Azoff, Irving, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00003 (Box 47)
    - B, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00004 (Box 47)
    - Barbour, Bernice, 2001; UA001.014.001.047.00005 (Box 47)
    - Becker, Edward, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00006 (Box 47)
    - Beaver, John, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00007 (Box 47)
    - Beda, Bruce, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00008 (Box 47)
    - Berenberg, Roslyn, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00009 (Box 47)
    - Berger, Albert, 1995; UA001.014.001.047.00010 (Box 47)
    - Black, Herbert, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00011 (Box 47)
    - Blair, Henry, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00012 (Box 47)
    - Block, Ellen, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00013 (Box 47)
    - Bristol, Eleanor, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00014 (Box 47)
    - Burns, Barbara, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00015 (Box 47)
    - Bzura, Bruce, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00016 (Box 47)
    - C, 1997 -- 2003; UA001.014.001.047.00017 (Box 47)
    - Cabot, John, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00018 (Box 47)
    - Cassidy, James E., 1996 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00019 (Box 47)
    - Chan, Anson, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00020 (Box 47)
    - Covas, George, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00021 (Box 47)
    - Charriol, Philippe, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00022 (Box 47)
    - D, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.047.00023 (Box 47)
    - Dalloul, Fakhri, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00024 (Box 47)
    - Dawood, Husain, 1996; UA001.014.001.047.00025 (Box 47)
    - Dreyfus, Jean-Paul, 1998; UA001.014.001.047.00026 (Box 47)
    - Duffet, Ethel, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00027 (Box 47)
    - E, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.047.00028 (Box 47)
    - F, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00029 (Box 47)
    - Fang, Harry, 1997; UA001.014.001.047.00030 (Box 47)
    - Feinburg, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00031 (Box 47)
    - Flagg, John, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00032 (Box 47)
    - Follett, David, 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00033 (Box 47)
    - Friedman, Robert, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00034 (Box 47)
    - G, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00035 (Box 47)
    - Gregorian, Arthur, 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00036 (Box 47)
    - Greisman, Harold, 2001; UA001.014.001.047.00037 (Box 47)
    - H, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.047.00038 (Box 47)
    - Hamill, John, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.047.00039 (Box 47)